<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Preset Filtered Zones (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.PresetFilteredZones</packageId>
  <author>cuproPanda</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/PresetFilteredZones</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of cuproPandas mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1210115905

- Included the [url=https://github.com/Proxyer/FZN]japanese translation[/url] by Proxyer
- Added support for translating the labels of the stockpiles
- Added presets to storage buildings and stockpiles

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/PresetFilteredZones][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Adds new stockpile zones which are already filtered for storing Meals, Meat, Vegetables, Medicine, Joy, Animals, etc. Storage creation is a breeze!

[h1]Workshop ID:[/h1]
1210115905

[h1]Zones Added:[/h1]
[b]Meal:[/b] A zone for rottable meals
[b]Medicine:[/b] A zone for anything in the medicine category
[b]Meat:[/b] A zone for meats other than human and insect
[b]Veg:[/b] A zone for rottable fruits, vegetables and edible seeds
[b]Joy:[/b] A zone for ingestibles that give joy when consumed. Includes drugs
[b]Animal:[/b] A zone for fresh animal corpses. Doesn't include insect or rotting corpses
[b]Outdoor:[/b] A zone for Items and Raw Resources that will not deteriorate outside
[b]Indoor:[/b] A zone for anything that deteriorates outside


[h1]Save Compatability[/h1]
This mod can be added to existing saves.
Always back up your saves before adding new mods as there is always the possibility for issues.

[h1]Mod Compatability[/h1]
[b]!!! Industrial Rollers:[/b] These zones are not recognized by Industrial Rollers and won't work. Zones are still usable for normal hauling.
No known issues yet, please report any issues

[h1]Older Versions and Update Notes[/h1]
All versions of this mod can be found on my [url=https://github.com/cuproPanda/Preset-Filtered-Zones/releases]GitHub[/url]. Each release has info on what has changed from the previous release.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>